[Shoot] Given his personality,
it's safe to assume
that he's already been won over.
I doubt he would knowingly sell me out,
[opening theme music playing]
[singer singing in English]
[singer singing in Japanese]
[narrator] There was a man
targeting Gon and Killua
and his name is Shoot McMahon.
[Killua grunts] No use.
The way we are now,
we don't stand a chance.
When I take my target down,
I'm always deliberate and thorough.
[boys grunting]
[Shoot] Go. This is it.
What's wrong?
It's the perfect opportunity.
I could easily just…
[grunts, shudders]
[straining] Go.
Go!
[groaning]
[continues weeping]
[Gon] Hey, Killua.
Why wasn't Mr. Knuckle good enough?
Wait. For what?
To get inside the NGL?
I mean, he's really strong.
I just don't get it.
I guess you're right.
It doesn't make any sense.
Physically he seems like
he'd be right on par with Kite.
Yeah, but his personality…
Why does that matter?
His philosophy isn't in line
with the mission's objective.
He's fragile.
And he gets attached to animals
way too easily.
[Gon] Yeah.
[imperceptible]
[Biscuit] They can maintain their Ren
for two hours
without even having to concentrate.
That's a good sign.
If they can do it for three hours,
I might let them fight
when they're fully rested.
I can only hope that
then they'll be able to realize
what they lack and what they need.
But that only gets them halfway.
If everything goes well,
it'll take them about ten days
to reach that point.
And that means they'll barely have
a day left before time is completely up.
I'm not convinced we can make it.
-[knife chopping]
-[Palm humming]
[Biscuit] If I want to save my own skin,
I should probably prepare an escape route.
-[Palm] Help yourself.
-[Gon and Killua] Thank you for the food!
[Palm] Not that.
We only have ten days left.
It looks to me like you're two-thirds
of the way through your training
which is meant to make you both
strong enough
to force Knuckle into using
his full power in battle.
[Biscuit] Uh-oh.
She knows exactly what's going on.
[Palm scoffs] But how can you be so sure?
You have no chance of beating Knuckle.
They didn't even give you enough time.
Lately, I find that I can calm myself
by staring at my knife,
and that can only mean I'm getting
dangerously close to losing it.
If you run away right now,
I probably won't hunt you down
and kill you.
Because you definitely can't win
as you are at the moment.
[sing-song]
I hereby swear that Killua and I
will take down Knuckle and Shoot
before the deadline comes.
I pinky-swear, so if I lie you can stick
a thousand needles right in my eye.
Where I'm from, we do this next.
-[heart beats]
-[Palm gasps]
There. Now it's a real promise.
By the way, Miss Palm,
what's in the broth?
[Palm breathing heavily]
Oh, it's from poultry.
I guess not everyone can handle her,
but Gon's getting better.
but I suspect
she's actually the one handling him.
I just put a kunai chicken
on to simmer overnight,
-then set it aside for later.
-Wow.
Well, ten days left.
-[Gon] It's awesome!
-You say that like we're screwed!
[Baital] This is it.
Baital Squad here.
What's the update, Goran?
Goran, do you read me? Hello?
Damn it! Did they get him already?
Is there anyone
from Goran's squad out there?
[Baital huffs]
These signals are getting all mashed up.
They should've established
a contact network
in case the leader goes missing.
Baital Squad, find Goran's squadron
and rendezvous with them.
Proceed in crane formation.
[grunting]
[grunts]
[Netero grunts]
So you're next, huh?
[Morel] You really think this is fair?
[Knov] What do you mean?
The Chairman is still much stronger
than we are.
And he seems rather excited.
[cell phone beeping]
[groans]
Hey, speak of the devil, huh?
You can keep sending them my way.
I'm finally starting
to get my groove back.
That's pretty impressive, sir.
[chuckles softly]
Then I think we can assume
that the King hasn't been born yet.
-[Morel] Roger that.
-[line disconnects]
He's old, but he's in top form.
-[Knov] Shall we go grab another squadron?
-Sure.
Gaftz's and Baital's squads
haven't returned yet.
We're down to 14 squads.
Those damned humans.
How in the world are they managing
to whittle us down like this?
No clue.
All I know is that there are some humans
out there who are quite powerful.
[sighs]
We know very little about them,
far less than I'm comfortable with.
Their powers appear so varied
and seem much stronger than our own.
If we just had more time,
Yes, I hope you're right.
[Queen laughing]
[liquid sloshes]
[gasps] Do you want to come out now?
[laughs]
Not yet.
It's still too early.
[Gon] Yeah. That seemed fast.
Then I suppose I'll give you a break,
take 30 minutes.
-Really?
-Aren't we supposed to fight Knuckle now?
I'll allow you two to go
once you're fully rested.
You can take him.
[both gasp]
The Chairman's deadline
is fast approaching.
Just over a day left.
So this may be
your first and final chance.
[boys grunt]
[Palm humming]
[muttering]
[Biscuit] The problem now
is how to escape?
Hmm?
[dogs snort]
You boys mean business tonight.
[violin music playing]
[violin music continues playing]
Hmm.
[footsteps thudding]
Good morning, Youpi.
I'm getting real hungry.
What? Are you talking about Shoot?
Yeah.
Why do you want to know about that?
You're about to get the crap
knocked out of you, kid.
Because we need both of your tiles.
You're just messing with me, right?
If you can beat me,
I'll answer your question.
We might not get a chance then,
not if your laying unconscious.
[grunts]
You just went too far
with that little joke.
[yelling]
[grunting]
Here!
-[Gon grunts]
-Gon!
[Gon] That hit hard.
I could feel it through my whole body.
Without Ken, his next punch
will definitely knock me out.
Four or five more warm-up punches,
and I'll get serious.
So you better watch yourselves, boys.
'Cause I get warmed up pretty damn fast.
Shall we make our move now?
We can wait until they're ready.
[Knov] Judging by the estimated number
of bodies currently stored in the nest,
they'll need to restock
in another week or so.
And whenever that happens,
I'd like to dispatch a few more squadrons.
[Netero] I leave that up to you.
[line disconnects]
We don't move from here
until we know how our pupils did.
Huh.
I think it's a waste of time.
Knuckle and Shoot can assist,
but the old man's kids
don't seem like they're all that reliable.
So we can't count on them in a battle.
The best we could hope for
is to use them as decoys.
I'll put down 100,000
on Knuckle and Shoot.
If neither of us wins,
the Chairman gets the money.
[Knov] Sure.
Then, I'll put…
one million on them.
Huh? There's no way in hell
they're gonna be ready by then.
What, are you trying
to throw all your money to the dogs?
The Chairman is a dog now?
[scoffs] I happen to love gambling.
And when it's a long shot, all the better.
[both grunting]
Behind you!
[gasps]
[grunts]
[Gon] This is supposed to be a warm up?
Damn, he's strong!
But why is Knuckle…
Could it be?
Come on, let me see that technique.
That "Show me rock" thing?
A small word of advice:
If you do try that attack,
then you're going down. [chuckles]
Your signature technique
currently has exactly two major flaws.
[closing theme music playing]
[singer singing in Japanese]
[upbeat music playing]
-And reassurance!
-[Biscuit] Oh, come on!
[singer singing in Japanese]